[wind blowing]
and then, he scattered them everywhere.
[dramatic music playing]
[door creaks open]
[intense music playing]
If there are any conditions
for Komugi's safe return, speak.
[Palm] He knows exactly what we're doing.
Why try to fool him?
What I felt when sensing your En
was not wrath or fear, or hate.
Shall I explain further?
It seems you doubt what you've just heard.
So, I'll say it again.
You are victorious. The battle is over.
-[gasps]
-I am here for a simple reason.
I have but one motive.
The human girl named Komugi.
We must speak.
There is truly nothing else
which I desire.
Even knowing what will happen,
I have but one great desire,
and that is to spend
my remaining time with Komugi.
And nothing more.
No, it's not. It's impossible.
You expect me to believe you? Seriously?
in order to fool someone as lowly as me.
After all the killing that you've done
and that you plan to do,
a creature such as you…
The King admits defeat?
He cares for a human?
No! It doesn't make sense.
He's doing this because it's the truth!
I believe that it was
only a minimal change.
[Palm] Huh?
[Meruem] Something, somewhere… shifted.
If only I had been this way
from the beginning.
I wanted to ask you
instead of searching myself.
What are you saying?
Stop this.
You're right.
I know exactly where Komugi is.
I don't think I have to tell you
that that is not a viable option now.
Your aura is strong and as starkly
beautiful as any I have ever seen.
[Palm] Stop it!
All that I can do now
is to ask you for your assistance.
No, don't!
I know what you mean to us as a species,
to go to such lengths.
I'll tell you.
But on one condition.
May I use my ability to watch,
to see your final moments with her?
If that is what you require,
then you have my permission.
I wanted to,
but I couldn't keep our promise.
[imperceptible]
[breathing heavily]
[Komugi] 4-7-1, King.
Let's play.
[rotors whirring]
[reporter] We have a shocking
breaking news update.
The reason that the dictator
of East Gorteau
assembled the entire country in one place
for a rally
has been revealed by our sources
to be genocide.
on a national level.
It's been reported that the whereabouts
of Bizeff, Diego's second in command,
are currently unknown.
We have spoken to several
informed sources,
who say this could have been
a military takeover.
As you know, dark rumors have long
swirled around East Gorteau and the NGL.
[camera shutter clicking]
This incident may provide
the perfect opportunity
No, I wasn't there to see it go down.
Sorry, it's too complicated to explain.
Anyway, we're waiting on Palm.
I'm sure one of your pencil pushers
would write a perfect follow-up report
if you really wanted.
I know how you guys are,
sitting at your comfortable desks,
in your air-conditioned rooms.
[sighs]
I'm afraid that logic simply won't fly
with the Vice-Chair camp.
[beeps]
[keyboard clacking]
Rest in peace.
You've certainly earned it.
[narrator] The same day,
a video was streamed online,
in which Netero announced his resignation
as chairman of the Hunter Association
effective immediately,
and gave instructions for choosing
his successor.
It was drowned out by other news
from the government-run media.
Only a select few understood
that it was his last will and testament.
[imperceptible]
[man] Come, raise a glass.
Let us drink to this creature
called "man."
That is why they yearn
and why they foster.
If they only knew
that all one needs in life is the sun,
ON A FARM, IN AN UNNAMED COUNTRY
[Palm] It's over.
Well, then. It feels like you and I
haven't played in forever!
Playing in real life is completely
different from playing in dreams.
-True.
-I could've sworn I felt someone kick me
really hard right in the stomach.
After that, there was this strange person
who kidnapped me.
And then, you must have saved me,
Dear Leader. So, thank you!
It wasn't me. Thank my guards.
Oh, no! I was wrong? I'm sorry!
I jumped to the wrong conclusion.
[Meruem] The fact is,
they were too good for me.
[Komugi] I'll have to remember
to thank them when they stop by.
Okay!
My name is Komugi, Lord Meruem.
It's such a great honor
to make your acquaintance.
I know it is. But no…
that's a lie. I knew nothing.
The truth of the matter is,
I didn't understand what truly mattered.
Silence! If I beat you at Gungi,
you will no longer use the honorific.
[gasps]
[Komugi] I understand.
But if I address you without it,
is that when I die?
[Meruem] Ah, that's right.
There is no need for you to die.
So, you should be prepared
for innumerable losses.
1-5-1, King.
[Meruem] 2-7-2, cannon.
Could it be?
Komugi, are you mocking me?
-[Komugi] No.
-Choose your words carefully.
I will not tolerate nonsense.
No, it's Gungi.
I never joke when I play Gungi.
Very well.
You lose, and I will take your life.
Yes.
[piece taps]
But all of them would only serve
to lengthen the game
without increasing her chances.
If she thinks there is an escape…
Now show me, what lies beyond!
[Komugi] 4-6-2, shinobi.
[Meruem gasps] This is…
she won't be able to deflect
the cavalry and duke.
to somebody like me.
Is that possible? It doesn't feel right.
You see, I have been poisoned,
playing with you, Komugi.
But this poison, it's contagious.
Stay by my side too long,
and you will also…
[Komugi] Lord Meruem, I want you to know,
I'm so happy right now.
I may not be worthy,
but please let me go with you.
[Meruem] Yes, I see it now.
[Meruem]
This is why I was born, for this moment!
[serene music playing]
SHINOBI - KING
[imperceptible]
[Komugi] 6-5-1, cavalry.
[Meruem] 2-7-2, new shinobi.
Komugi, are you there?
[Meruem] It would appear that
I never defeated you.
[Komugi] 9-5-1, King.
[Meruem] Komugi, are you there?
[Komugi] Of course, I am. Go ahead.
It's your turn, Lord Meruem.
[Meruem]
I feel rather tired. I shall sleep.
Just a short while.
[Komugi] I can hear you. All right.
Like this?
[Meruem] I shall wake up shortly.
-[Meruem] Thank you.
-[Komugi] You're welcome.
[Meruem] Will you say my name…
one last time?
[Komugi] Good night, Meruem.
It'll be all right.
I'll be joining you soon.
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time,
"Homecoming and True Name."
[singer singing in Japanese]